tuningnews.net 2009-02-27

# Privacy Policy - tuningnews.net

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to protecting your privacy at tuningnews.net. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement. 

**Cookies**

Like many other Web sites, tuningnews.net uses cookies to identify members so they don't have to re-enter a user id and password when they, for example, wish to post to a discussion. Cookies also help us improve your experience and display more prominently goods and services that might interest you. If you do not have cookies enabled, you must enter your password each time you access our site or any of its member features. 

**Third parties**

tuningnews.net may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member, unless that member has given us permission to share that information. We may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we can get a better understanding of traffic through our site and thus improve our content offerings. tuningnews.net also may use third party companies to provide delivery of e-mail newsletters and other messages over e-mail. 

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

**Security**

We use reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose both in your browsing and your purchases and to only release this information to third parties we believe share our commitment to privacy. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties. 

**Obtaining your consent**

By using our Web site, you give tuningnews.net permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at tuningnews.net, you authorize tuningnews.net to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. tuningnews.net may occasionally amend this policy. We suggest that you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time. 

**Questions?**

If you wish to change any information you have given us, or have any questions on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at info [at] "our domain name"
